28 Years Later Part 3 is a horror, thriller, science
fiction film directed by Danny Boyle.
The third installment in the 28 Days Later sequel trilogy.
Jim, played by Cillian Murphy.
Spike, played by Alfie Williams.
Kelly, played by Erin Kellyman.
Sam, played by Maiya Eastmond.
28 Years Later is a 2025 post-apocalyptic coming-of-age horror-drama film
produced and directed by Danny Boyle and written by Alex Garland.
The third film in the 28 Days Later film series, it stars Jodie Comer, Aaron
Taylor-Johnson, Jack O'Connell, Alfie Williams, and Ralph Fiennes.
The film tells the story of a boy living in a post-apocalyptic world who undertakes a hazardous
journey with his ill mother in an effort to obtain medical treatment for her.
28 Years Later marks the returns of Boyle, Garland and
cinematographer Anthony Dod Mantle to the film series.
Cillian Murphy, who starred in the first film, served as executive producer.
The film was shot back-to-back with its sequel, 28 Years Later: The Bone Temple,
which was directed by Nia DaCosta and released in January 2026.
28 Years Later was released in the United Kingdom and the United States by Sony
Pictures Releasing through its Columbia Pictures label on 20 June 2025.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics and grossed
$151 million worldwide against a budget of $60 million.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking and intense.